southernhospitalityblog.com 2019-06-02

# Privacy Policy - Southern Hospitality

**New Updated Privacy Policy as of May 2018**

This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behaviour on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact AdThrive at [info@adthrive.com](mailto:info@adthrive.com). If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences icon. (Available in the EU.)

 **Effective as of May 25, 2018**

As the owner of this website (the “Site”), **Southern Hospitality  **(“we” or “us”) understand that your privacy is of critical importance.  This Privacy Policy describes what information we collect from you via the Site and how we use and disclose such information.

We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google’s privacy policy is available at: <https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/>

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies and to delete cookies. The methods for doing so vary from browser to browser, and from version to version. You can however obtain up-to-date information about blocking and deleting cookies via these links:

(a) <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en> (Chrome);

(b) <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences>(Firefox);

(c) <http://www.opera.com/help/tutorials/security/cookies/> (Opera);

(d) <https://support.microsoft.com/en-gb/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies> (Internet Explorer);

(e) <https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411> (Safari); and

(f) <https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy> (Edge).

Please note that blocking cookies may have a negative impact on the functions of many websites, including our Site. Some features of the Site may cease to be available to you.

 **We Collect and Process Personal Data**

When visiting [Southern Hospitality](https://southernhospitalityblog.com/), your personal data may be collected. Most of our web pages contain information which does not require any personal information from the web site visitor. However, in some cases we need to collect and store personal data in order to provide services or information that you request from the website. At Southern Hospitality we collect information regarding your website behaviour and your communication and interaction on this site. This information may be connected to existing personal data that has been stored for a specified and defined purpose.

* * *

 **How Southern Hospitality collects and processes your personal data**

Southern Hospitality controls all of the personal data that you share with us when you:

~Visit our web site and accept cookies  
~Contact us by form or by e-mail  
~Are a customer, partner or have entered into a process to become customer or partner  
~Sign up for any of our notifications and newsletters  
~Download material that requires you to submit a form  
~Subscribe to our blog

Your personal information will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, nor given to any other company for any reason whatsoever without your consent. The only exception to this might be the express purpose of delivering an ordered product or service requested by the customer.

 **Why we process personal data**

Southern Hospitality processes personal data and relevant information that is needed to properly provide our services and/or enhance the experience of visiting our site. We need to process personal data in order to administrate user accounts, manage notifications, digital marketing and re-marketing. If you no longer want to receive digital notifications and/or marketing, you can unsubscribe. There is an unsubscribe button at the bottom of each email.

We store non-sensitive data about our customer. For example, first and last name, email address, comments.

Some additional ways that Southern Hospitality may collect and store your data includes but is not limited to the following:

~ User Registration

~ Comments

~ Contact Form Entries

~ Analytics & Traffic Log Solutions

~ Logging Tools & Plugins

 ~ Security Tools & Plugins

 ~ Order Forms & Purchases

 **Security**

The security of your personal data is important to us. We adhere to the law, regulations and general recommendations within our business sector, regarding security of the personal information that is shared with us. This applies to the submissions and storage of data.

However, our website visitors should be aware that there is no way to transfer and store data electronically that is 100% secure.

 **About cookies**

Southern Hospitality is using cookies. A cookie is a small text document that is stored on your computer, containing information used to enhance the website for you.

There are two types of cookies. A permanent cookie that saves a file on your computer to enhance the website depending on your choices, interests or the fact that you have previously visited the website.

A session cookie is sent between the server and your computer during your visit and disappears when you close your browser.

Our website is using both permanent cookies and session cookies. Permanent cookies are used to avoid requesting repeats of one-time information and session cookies are used to enable you to login to our services.

If you do not agree with the usage of cookies you can turn cookies off in your browser’s security settings. There are also settings allowing your browser to show you a warning every time the browser is trying to put a cookie on your computer.

 **About beacon tracking and scripts**

Southern Hospitality uses web beacon tracking and scripts from third party suppliers which, on behalf of Southern Hospitality collects information about how website visitors use and communicate with the website. This way we can see how we acquire web traffic, which parts of the website that are most used and which links visitors click most. We use this information to further improve and develop the content of our website and our digital advertising.

 **Questions regarding our privacy policy**

By visiting our website and submitting your personal information, you accept that your personal data will be processed according to this privacy policy. You may also be requested to provide your authorization for any personal data that may be collected and stored.

Southern Hospitality reserves the right to revise the privacy policy without prior notice. Therefore we ask you to review this policy now and check it regularly if you are a frequent visitor to our website.
